

# **PROFILE**

I'm an 18 years old Game development student. Raised in IJsselstein and living in Nieuwegein. Since 2020 I have been studying game development at Grafisch Lyceum Utrecht.

My Passion is to create great games and learn as much as I can along the way.

have an interest in all aspects of game development, but have especially been enjoying UI and character control tools. Big projects are where I really shine. I'm most motivated when I have a

# CONTACT

PHONE: +31 6 245 677 51

WEBSITE: TychovanEngelenburg.nl

strong team to build on.

EMAIL: TychovanEngelenburg@gmail.com

# **HOBBIES**

Gaming
Programming
Playing instruments
Collecting things

# TYCHO VAN ENGELENBURG

Game developer

# **EDUCATION**

#### Anna van Rijn college

2016 - 2020

VMBO-TL Bilingual, Profile Economy and care, subject: IT

#### **Grafisch Lyceum Utrecht**

2020 - 2024

Mbo Level 4 BOL, Profile Game development/Game design

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Bouwspeeltuin Bouwgein - Voluteer

2018 - 2021

Helping children use wood to build forts. Signing in and out children and parents. Helping at the vacation activities.

## Dag van de Techniek - Volunteer

2019 - Current

1 Weekend every year I help out at the technics day. This day is meant to show children what it's like to work in a technical field.

# Jumbo - Shelf stocker

Jun 2020 - Dec 2020

Making sure all shelves are properly stocked. Helping customers with any issues they might have.

#### Bram Ladage - Fry baker

Jun 2022 - oct 2022

Cutting potatoes, Baking fries, Taking orders, Delivering food.

# **SKILLS**

B2-C1 Level English Scrum Communication Taking initiative